<?xml version="1.0"?>
<!--Created by XmlShell on 10/31/2007 3:03:11 PM-->
<Astrosoft>
	<YogaCombinations>
		<YogaCombination Name="AdhiYoga">
			<Definition>If benefics are situated in the 6th, 7th and 8th from the Moon, the combination goes  under the name of Adhi Yoga.</Definition>
			<Results>The person will be polite and trustworthy, will have an enjoyable and happy life, surrounded by luxuries and affluence, will inflict defeats on his enemies, will be healthy and will live long.</Results>
		</YogaCombination>
		<YogaCombination Name="AmalaYoga">
			<Definition>The 10th from the Moon or Lagna should be occupied by a benefic planet</Definition>
			<Results>The person will achieve lasting fame and reputation. His character will be spotless and he will lead a prosperous life.</Results>
		</YogaCombination>
		<YogaCombination Name="AnaphaYoga">
			<Definition>If  there are planets in the 12th from the Moon, Anapha Yoga is formed.</Definition>
			<Results>Well-formed organs,   majestic appearance, good reputation, polite, generous, self-respect, fond of dress and sense Pleasures. In the later life' renunciation  and austerity.</Results>
		</YogaCombination>
		<YogaCombination Name="BudhaAdityaYoga">
			<Definition>If Mercury combines with the Sun,  the combination goes under the name of Budha-Aditya Yoga.</Definition>
			<Results>Highly intelligent, skilful in all works, good reputation, personal respect and surrounded by all comforts and happiness.</Results>
		</YogaCombination>
		<YogaCombination Name="ChandraManglaYoga">
			<Definition>If Mars conjoins the Moon this yoga is formed.</Definition>
			<Results>Earnings through unscrupulous means, a seller of women, treating mother harshly &amp; doing mischief to her &amp; other relatives.</Results>
		</YogaCombination>
		<YogaCombination Name="ChatussagaraYoga">
			<Definition>Chatussagara Yoga is caused when all the kendras are occupied by planets.</Definition>
			<Results>The person will earn good reputation, be an equal to a ruler, have a long and prosperous life, be blessed with good children and health and his name will travel to the confines of the four oceans.</Results>
		</YogaCombination>
		<YogaCombination Name="DhurdhuraYoga">
			<Definition>If there are planets on either side of the Moon, the combination goes under the name of Dhurdhura.</Definition>
			<Results>The native is bountiful. He will be blessed with much wealth and conveyances.</Results>
		</YogaCombination>
		<YogaCombination Name="GajakesariYoga">
			<Definition>If  Jupiter is in a kendra from the Moon the combination goes under the name Gajakesari.</Definition>
			<Results>Many relations, polite and generous, builder of villages and towns or magistrate over them ; will have a lasting reputation even long after death.</Results>
		</YogaCombination>
		<YogaCombination Name="KemadrumaYoga">
			<Definition>When there are no planets on both  sides of the Moon, Kemadruma Yoga is formed.</Definition>
			<Results>The person will be dirty, sorrowful, doing unrighteous deeds, poor, dependent, a rogue and a swindler.</Results>
		</YogaCombination>
		<YogaCombination Name="RajalakshanaYoga">
			<Definition> Jupiter, Venus, Mercury and Moon should be in Lagna or they should be placed in Kendra.</Definition>
			<Results>The native will possess an attractive appearance and he will be endowed with all the good qualities of high personages.</Results>
		</YogaCombination>
		<YogaCombination Name="SunaphaYoga">
			<Definition>If  there are planets (excepting the Sun) in the second house from the Moon, Sunapha is caused.</Definition>
			<Results>Self-earned property, king, ruler or his equal, intelligent, wealthy and good reputation.</Results>
		</YogaCombination>
		<YogaCombination Name="VasumathiYoga">
			<Definition>If benefics occupy the upachayas  (3, 6, 10 and 11) either from the ascendant or from the Moon, the combination goes under the name of Vasumathi Yoga.</Definition>
			<Results>The person will not be a dependent but will always command plenty of wealth.</Results>
		</YogaCombination>
		<YogaCombination Name="SubhaVesiYoga">
			<Definition>If planets   other than  the Moon  occupy the 2nd from the Sun, Vesi Yoga is formed.</Definition>
			<Results> The person will be fortunate,   happy, virtuous, famous and aristocratic.</Results>
		</YogaCombination>
		<YogaCombination Name="PapaVesiYoga">
			<Definition>If planets   other than  the Moon  occupy the 2nd from the Sun, Vesi Yoga is formed.</Definition>
			<Results> The person will be fortunate,   happy, virtuous, famous and aristocratic.</Results>
		</YogaCombination>
		<YogaCombination Name="SubhaVasiYoga">
			<Definition>Planets other than the Moon occupying the 12th from the Sun give rise to Vasi Yoga.</Definition>
			<Results>The subject will be happy, prosperous, liberal and the favourite of the ruling classes.</Results>
		</YogaCombination>
		<YogaCombination Name="PapaVasiYoga">
			<Definition>Planets other than the Moon occu&#173;pying the 12th from the Sun give rise to Vasi Yoga.</Definition>
			<Results>The subject will be happy, prosperous, liberal and the favourite of the ruling classes.</Results>
		</YogaCombination>
		<YogaCombination Name="ObhayachariYoga">
			<Definition>If planets other than the Moon are  present on either side of the Sun, Obhayachari is caused.</Definition>
			<Results>The person will be an eloquent speaker. Will have well-proportioned limbs, will take delight in everything, will be liked by all, wealthy and famous.</Results>
		</YogaCombination>
		<YogaCombination Name="HamsaYoga">
			<Definition>Jupiter   should occupy a Kendra  which should be his own house or exaltation sign.</Definition>
			<Results>His legs will have the markings of a conch, lotus, fish and ankusa. He will possess a hand&#173;some body; he will be liked by others; he will be righteous in disposition and pure in mind.</Results>
		</YogaCombination>
		<YogaCombination Name="MalavyaYoga">
			<Definition>Venus should occupy a quadrant which should be his own or exaltation sign.</Definition>
			<Results>The person will have a well-developed physique, will be strong-minded, wealthy, happy with children and wife, will command vehicles, endowed with clean sense-organs and renowned and learned. </Results>
		</YogaCombination>
		<YogaCombination Name="SasaYoga">
			<Definition>Sasa Yoga is given rise to if Saturn  occupies a Kendra which should be his own or exaltation sign.</Definition>
			<Results>One born in this Yoga will command good servants. His character will be questionable. He will be head of a village or a town or even a King, will covet other's riches &amp; will be wicked in disposition.</Results>
		</YogaCombination>
		<YogaCombination Name="RuchakaYoga">
			<Definition>Mars should be exalted in a Kendra  or occupy a Kendra which should be his own sign.</Definition>
			<Results>The person born in Ruchaka will have a strong physique, famous, well-versed in ancient lore, King or an equal to a King, conforming to traditions &amp; customs. He will have a ruddy complexion, attractive body, charitable disposition, wealthy, long-lived &amp; leader of an army.</Results>
		</YogaCombination>
		<YogaCombination Name="BhadraYoga">
			<Definition>Bhadra Yoga is caused by the disposition of Mercury in a Kendra which should be identical with his own or exaltation sign.</Definition>
			<Results>The person born in Bhadra Yoga will be strong, will have a lion-like face, well-developed chest, well-proportioned limbs, will be taciturn, will help relatives &amp; will live up to a good old age.</Results>
		</YogaCombination>
		<YogaCombination Name="KusumaYoga">
			<Definition>If jupiter is in lagna, the moon in the 7th and the sun is the 8th from the moon, Kusuma Yoga is caused.</Definition>
			<Results>The person will be a King or equal to a King, protector of kith and kin, founder of a town or a headman, and possessed of unsullied reputation.</Results>
		</YogaCombination>
		<YogaCombination Name="JayaYoga">
			<Definition>When the lord of the 6th is debilitated  and the lord of the 10th is deeply exalted Jaya Yoga will arise.</Definition>
			<Results>The native will be happy, victorious  over his enemies, successful in all his ventures and long-lived.</Results>
		</YogaCombination>
		<YogaCombination Name="SivaYoga">
			<Definition>If the lord of the 5th is in the 9th, the lord of the 9th is in the 10th and the lord of the 10th is in the 5th, Siva Yoga is caused.</Definition>
			<Results>The person will be a big trader, a con&#173;queror and commander of armies; he will possess divine wisdom and will lead a virtuous life.</Results>
		</YogaCombination>
		<YogaCombination Name="ChapaYoga">
			<Definition>If the Ascendant lord is exalted and  the 4th and 10th lords have interchanged houses, Chapa Yoga is caused.</Definition>
			<Results>The person will grace a King's Council, be wealthy and full of strength and an Exchequer or a Comptroller of treasury.</Results>
		</YogaCombination>
		<YogaCombination Name="KahalaYoga">
			<Definition>Lords of the fourth and ninth houses  should be in Kendras from each other and the lord of Lagna should be strongly disposed.</Definition>
			<Results>The native will be stubborn, not well informed, daring, head of a small army and a few villages.</Results>
		</YogaCombination>
		<YogaCombination Name="LakshmiYoga">
			<Definition>If the lord of Lagna is powerful and the lord of the 9th occupies own or exaltation sign identical with a Kendra or Thrikona, Lakshmi Yoga is caused.</Definition>
			<Results>The person will be wealthy, noble, learned, a man of high integrity and reputation, handsome appearance, a good ruler, and enjoying all the pleasures and comforts of life.</Results>
		</YogaCombination>
		<YogaCombination Name="MahabhagyaYoga">
			<Definition>In the case of a man, when the birth  is during daytime the Sun, the Moon and the Lagna should be in odd signs. </Definition>
			<Results>A male born under this Yoga will have good character, will be a source of pleasure to others, will be liberal, generous, famous, a ruler or an equal to him and lives to a good old age. A female born in this combination will be blessed with long-lived children &amp; wealth &amp; she will be of good conduct.</Results>
		</YogaCombination>
	</YogaCombinations>
</Astrosoft>
